mytutorialscafe.com 2014-12-24

# Privacy Policy | My Tutorials Cafe

We may collect **Personal Identification Information (PII)** from users in different ways such as, a user visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other resources we have made available on our site. User may visit our site anonymously. We will collect **PII** from users only if they willingly submit such information to us. Visitors can always refuse to provide **PII,** except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

###  **2\. Log Files**

**MyTutorialsCafe** makes use of log files through **Google Analytics.** The information inside the log files includes Internet Protocol **(IP)** Addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider **(ISP)** , Date/Time Stamp, Referring/Exit Pages & No. of Clicks to analyze Trends, Administer the Site, Track User’s Movement around the site, and gather Demographic Information. IP Addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

###  3\. How MyTutorialsCafe Use Collected Information?

We collect and use User Personal Information for the following purposes:

  * **To Personalize Your Experience**

        _(Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)_

  * **To Improve Our Website**

      _  (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)_

_(The email address user provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions)_

###  4\. How MyTutorialsCafe Protect Your Information?

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our site. We protect your information in the following manner:

"The email addresses collected via subscriptions to the **MyTutorialsCafe** newsletters are not sold, or disclosed to any third parties. These addresses will only be used by our site to send out **MyTutorialsCafe** communications (such as, the **MyTutorialsCafe** newsletters, plug-in information and updates). The email addresses collected at **MyTutorialsCafe** are stored on a secure dedicated server. Your information will neither be spam & never be sold, share or trade with anyone".

###  5\. Third-Party Websites

Users may find advertising or other content on **MyTutorialsCafe** that link to the sites of other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. In addition, these sites, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

###  6\. Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non- personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

###  7\. Cookies and Web Beacons

**MyTutorialsCafe** does use cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **MyTutorialsCafe**. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to **MyTutorialsCafe** and other sites on the Internet. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on **MyTutorialsCafe** send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. **MyTutorialsCafe** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

###  8\. Changes To This Privacy Policy

**MyTutorialsCafe** has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information of users we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

###  9\. Your Acceptance To Terms & Conditions

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance to this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

###  10\. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please **[contact us.](http://www.mytutorialscafe.com/p/contact.html)**

_Kind Regards._
